KATIE TUNSTALL

UX/UI DESIGNER

CONTACT ME AT

Available remotely, currently in Perth, Western Australia

+61 4

+61 452 238 835

katietunstall@icloud.com

www.katietunstallux.com

in

katie-tunstall

UX SKILLS

Heuristic analysis

Persona creation

User research & studies

Usability testing

Prototyping & Wireframing

Card sorting & Affinity mapping

Task analysis & Journey maps

Information architecture

TOOLS SUMMARY

Adobe XD

Digital design

Adobe Photoshop & Lightroom

Optimal workshop

Miro

Jira & Slack

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a UX/UI designer with a background in photography and business. Having worked worldwide in the UK, South Africa and Australia, I have gained wide experience in project management and creative solutions with the user at the forefront.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance UX/UI Designer

Katie Tunstall UX | Feb 2018 - present

 Under the lead designer, I designed website UI using using Adobe XD, with a focus on UX. Enhanced UX on existing websites using heuristics analysis. Annotated and collated findings from online user testing sessions.

Freelance photographer

Katie Tunstall Photography | Feb 2018 - present

• Worked in collaboration with a web design agency helping clients rebrand business imagery. Responsible for creating briefs and providing end finished deliverables.

Senior photographer & Designer

Verve Portraits | May 2012 - Dec 2017

- Founded Verve Portraits with a team of 3 photographers.
- Oversaw and ran various departments for a successful high-end photography & sales studio with a current turnover of \$13m

PROJECTS

Orms, Cape Town, South Africa

Project Manager | May 2011 - Feb 2012

 Co-ordinated a team of web developers and designers to create an SAAS project for an online photography production company. Was responsible for research and overall running of project to completion.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

CareerFoundry

UX Immersion | Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

- Completing the design of a mobile app, focusing on understanding the user, research, wire-framing, prototyping, usability testing & UI design.
- Specialising in front end development.

Interaction Design Foundation

Usability testing & HCI | May 2017 - Feb 2018

- Understanding and conducting UX practices.
- Understanding users & how to implement user-centered design for best results.